[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Stockings are _ socks",
    "options": ["big", "small", "long", "short"],
    "answer": "long"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "She told me his name after he _ .",
    "options": ["left", "had left", "has left", "has been leaving"],
    "answer": "had left"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Climate is a _ of the environment.",
    "options": ["rank", "situation", "state", "size"],
    "answer": "state"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "I finally killed the fly _ a rolled up newspaper.",
    "options": ["by", "through", "with", "from"],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "We must look pleased or else he'll be _",
    "options": ["happy", "cross", "dissatisfied", "dissatisfied delighted"],
    "answer": "dissatisfied"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The man died _ over eating.",
    "options": ["by", "of", "for", "from"],
    "answer": "from"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "He advised me _ smoking .",
    "options": ["giving up", "to give up", "in giving up", "from giving up"],
    "answer": "to give up"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The expression 'After one's own heart' means :",
    "options": [
      "with complete devotion",
      "To one's own liking",
      "To be in low spirit",
      "To be in high spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "To one's own liking"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "'The day of my sistet's marriage is drawing near---'. The underlined word is a/an -",
    "options": ["verb", "preposition", "adverb", "adjective"],
    "answer": "adverb"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which is the following sentence is the correct one ?",
    "options": [
      "My father was in hospital for six weeks during the summer",
      "My father was in a hospital during six weeks in summer",
      "In summer during six weeks my father was in hospital",
      "My father was in hospital during six weeks in summer"
    ],
    "answer": "My father was in hospital for six weeks during the summer"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "He intends to _ in the country for two months .",
    "options": ["live", "stay", "stop", "halt"],
    "answer": "stay"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What are you so angry _ ?",
    "options": ["with", "about", "at", "for"],
    "answer": "about"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The parents become extremely _ when their son had not returned by eleven o'clock.",
    "options": ["angry", "annoyed", "disturbed", "anxious"],
    "answer": "anxious"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "\"\"\"I _ remember the holiday I spent in your home,\"\" she said.\"",
    "options": ["always", "usually", "hardly", "ever"],
    "answer": "always"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "He knew it was a avery _ operation, but he was determined to carry it out .",
    "options": ["dangerous", "risky", "difficult", "troublesome"],
    "answer": "risky"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "'Misanthropist' means :",
    "options": [
      "one who believe that God is in everything",
      "One who first with ladies",
      "A hater of mankind",
      "A person of narrow views"
    ],
    "answer": "A hater of mankind"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "First language means the _ language .",
    "options": ["important", "main", "offical", "natural"],
    "answer": "natural"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Shaheen would never have taken the job if _ what great demand it would make on his time .",
    "options": [
      "he was knowing",
      "he knew",
      "he had been knowing",
      "he had known"
    ],
    "answer": "he had known"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "She has _ her hair a beautiful shade of brown .",
    "options": ["dried", "dyed", "given", "colored"],
    "answer": "dyed"
  }
]
